



SUMMARY

I am a passionate, creative problem solver, who believes in the power of a good team. I am a web developer and designer who loves coding design and designing code. I have been studying web development and design for over three years and recently graduated from the Iron Yard (a three month immersive web development program).

EXPERIENCE

- Recent graduate of a three month immersive UI development and design program, called the Iron Yard, in Raleigh, NC.

 Gained the relevent skills and knowledge in order to be a successful front-end developer who is always adapting, growing and learning.
- Designed and developed several projects including two collaborations with back-end developers.
- Am in the discovery phase of two development and design freelance projects.
- Studied web development and design for three years at Wake Technical Community College.

SKILLS

HTML5 GIT

CSS3 GITHUB

SASS ILLUSTRATOR
BOOTSTRAP PHOTOSHOP

JQUERY INVISION

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT
USER FOCUSED DESIGN
RESPONSIVE DESIGN
WIREFRAMING
PROTOTYPING

PROJECTS

BIKE MD

A web application designed to foster a community of motorcycle techs in order to assist each other with troubleshooting.

lead front end developer assistant designer

BRANCHLESS BANK

A mobile application design for a hypothetical online only bank. *designed all wireframing, mockups, and prototypes*

GOODREADS

A redisign of the bookshelf page of the goodreads website. Designed a new logo, cleaned up the page and added space.

handled all front-end design and development

EMPLOYMENT

MORNING TIMES (2011-2016)

Barista. But the heart of the job was playing an active role in the community by treating customers how I would want to be treated and honestly listening to them.

HELIOS (2008-2011)

Barista

PORT CITY JAVA (2004-2006)

Barista.

YMCA (1999-2004)

Youth activities program director. Full time counselor.

EDUCATION

THE IRON YARD (2016 - 2017)

UI DEVELOPMENT / DESIGN

WAKE TECHNICAL COLLEGE (2013-2016)

WEB DEVELOPMENT / DESIGN

EAST CAROLINA UNIVERSITY (1996-1999)

COMMUNICATIONS

A LITTLE MORE...

- I PLAY GUITAR AND SING IN THE BAND GRAY YOUNG. WE HAVE THREE ALBUMS AND ONE EP.
- I LOVE PEOPLE, AND I WILL TAKE A GOOD CONVERSATION OVER A MOVIE.